第一次打板
Take one. Mark.
准备好了就跟我们说
Let us know when you're ready
这个新产品 提供的是社群
What this new product offers is community
安全 可靠的社群 使其更加丰富的是
Safe, secure community, enriched with
大家能与韦斯达备受喜爱的
the integrated interactions with the cherished family
影视人物 进行密切交流
of Way star's movie and TV characters.
我相信 我们的“生活+”房地产品牌
I'm convinced that the Living Plus real estate brand
可以让邮轮体验正式登陆
can bring the cruise ship experience to dry land
并为我们的乐园部门
and provide a significant boost to the earnings
带来丰厚进账
of our parks division.
我本人十分兴奋
I couldn't be more excited.
而且...  -可以打断一下吗
And I...   -Can I stop you there?
抱歉 原本的想法是…
Sorry, the... The thought is…
我们可以…再来一次吗
Can we may be do just... just one more.
原本的想法 是要轻松一点
The thought was just maybe a touch more upbeat
原本的想法?
That was the thought, was it?
就是尽量…
Just be good to
拍好一点
get it as good as it can be
你觉得 要尽量
You think we should get it
拍好一点吗
"as good as it can be "?
你说“兴奋”两个字的时候
Could... Could you may be sound
可以兴奋一点吗
more excited when you say the word "excited "?
好吧 抱歉 他的脸有点反光
Okay. So... He's a little shiny
能不能让... 安琪拉 你在边上吗
Can we... Can we get... Angela, are you nearby?
有点反光 谢谢
Just a little shine. Thank you
别烦我了 行不行
Can you please stop buzzing around me?
天啊 你们这帮家伙 真够没用的
God, you're fucking useless, the lot of you
跟我的白痴孩子们一样差劲
You're as bad my fucking idiot kids
那些…都是屁话
That's... That's bullshit.
抱歉 肯
Sorry... sorry, Ken.
没关系 这话对他而言 算是情话了
That... that's fine. That's a Valentine's card
可以再看一次吗
Could we watch it again, actually?
没问题
Absolutely
爸 看到你真好
Good to see you, Dad
继   承   之   战
第 4 季  第 6 集
我相信 我们的“生活+”房地产品牌...
I'm convinced that the Living Plus real estate brand.
嘿  -嘿
Hey.   -Hey.
所以呢 所以什么
So?   -So, what?
你飞了三千公里
What, you came 3000 kilometers
却不愿意再多走二十米吗
and you can't come another 20 meters?
是的
Yeah,
我只是挑了个方便的地方加点油
see, I'm just stopping at a convenient location to refuel
没理由下飞机 所以…
and there is no reason for me to get off the plane. So...
再见
Bye.
嘿
Hey.
嗨  -嘿
Hi.   -Hey
好乏味的装潢
Tired interior.
别批评我飞机的装潢 这样我很受伤
Don't criticize my jet interior. It hurts.
那么...  -没事 没事
So?   -Nothing. Nothing...
只是想来问问
Just thought I'd check in, you know
产品发表和投资人的那档事
With the whole, the whole product launch, investor thing?
生活+  -对
Living Plus.   -Yeah
你做这玩意干嘛
Why... why are you doing this bullshit?
事先已经安排好的
Well, it's on the calendar
如果我们决定取消产品发表
And if we decided to cancel the product launch.
会让人觉得 我们只是在看家
it would look like we were just minding the shop
等你进驻  -但 本来就是啊 不是吗
until you came in.   -Well, you are, right?
我不需要这个
I don't... I don't need it
这他妈是地上邮轮
It's fucking Land Cruises.
是生活+
Living Plus.
“生活+”...  -对
Li... " Living Plus."   -Yeah
才怪 就是地上邮轮
No, it's... it's Land Cruises.
你知道被关在邮轮上的感觉
'Hey. You know how shitty and heartbreaking it is
有多惨吗
being locked up on a cruise?
除此之外 你还可以
How about that, but you also get to stay
一直待在同一个地方
in the same fucking place the whole time?"
我不会特别去经营这个 你们干嘛要宣布
I'm not gonna pursue, so why would you announce?
你这样说太过分了,  -好了
Well, that's presumptuous.   -Okay.
我的情况是这样...
So, here's my situation...
我们的交易 会快速定案
The deal is going through, with velocity
其中 很多部分 你们之中有很多人 我都很喜欢
and lots of it... Lots of you I... I really like
但 其中也很多部分 我很不喜欢
But lots of it I also really hate.
也有很多地方我完全不想进去 好吗
Lots of rooms I never want to go into, okay?
所以...如果...
So there's... There's a..
如果内部有人…除了了解这一切之外
If there's someone on the inside who... who understands all that
还很懂我...
but also gets me...
那会...
That could be...
很有价值
could be of, value
天啊  -别这样 我们是哥儿们
God.   -Come on. We're buddies.
不能好好聊聊吗  -不 说不定我很讨厌你
Can we just talk, like...   -No, may be I hate you
不可能的 你还不够了解我
No, you can't hate me, you don't know me well enough
也许我很爱我的哥哥们
May be I love my brothers very much
对了 他们有没有跟你说
By the way, did they mention
他们在翁达尔斯内斯
that they went totally fucking mental on me
对我发火的事
up above Andalsnes?
很不专业 也蠢到极点
Totally unprofessional, totally dumb
听着 你想说的都说了 我也听了 但是 我得走了
Look. You spoke, I listened, but I... I gotta go now
我想我的...我能...我的飞机要起飞了
I think my... Yeah, I can... My flight's leaving.
对 发动引擎
Yeah. Start the engines!
好吧 有什么事 随时跟我说
Okay. Well, you keep me looped.
你是我的内部女孩  -死去吧你
My girl on the inside.   -Fuck you,
我的外部男孩
my boy on the outside.
我要把你说的话 全部告诉我的哥哥们
You know, I'm gonna tell my brothers everything you said
行 说吧
Cool. Do that.
我没什么见不得人的 要我自己跟他们说都行
Nothing to hide, nothing I wouldn't tell them myself.
好吧
Okay.
祝你的洛杉矶之行愉快  -再见
Enjoy L. A.   -Bye.
嘿 欢迎  -嘿 嘿 早安
Hey. Welcome.   -Hey, hey. Morning.
早  -欢迎
Morning.   -Welcome
谢谢 谢谢大家抽空出席
Thanks. Thanks for, everybody, for finding time.
两位CEO要亲自告诉我们一些…
Our CEOs wanted to give us a sensitive..
是的
Yeah.
最新的机密谈判内容 对吗
In-person update on negotiations, correct?
对 谢谢各位大驾光临
Correct. Yeah. Thanks. Thanks for being here, guys
我知道 你们在忙”投资者日”的事
I know everybody's swamped with, Investor Day
我们又有产品发布
and we've... We've got the product launch
所以…我会长话短说 但是
so... so... so, I'll make this brief, but..
抱歉 小西
Did I... I'm sorry, Shiv.
是这样 整体而言 我很兴奋
Look... Overall, very excited
非常兴奋
Super excited.
但 关于马特森对这个行业的了解
Just, questions about, Mats son's full understanding
我还有些疑问
of the whole business
我们对谈到的价钱非常满意
We're... we're pleased with the offer we extracted
价钱很好
It's... The price is great.
这是你们立的大功
I mean, you knocked it out of the park, guys
我是说真的  -谢了
I mean, really.   -Thanks!
同意 同意 不过
Hear, hear. Hear, hear. But it's just.
在我们准备董事会推荐的同时
as... a s we're preparing our board recommendation,
我们想跟 资深的各位 分享一些机密内容
we wanted to share some confidential context
并寻求各位的建议
with this senior group and seek your advice
我长话短说 马特森有一些
Yeah. I mean, long story short, Mats son exhibited some
可以说是怪异的举止 让我们有点担心
what you'd call erratic behavior that made us concerned.
到底发生了什么事
What... Well, what exactly happened?
这个...是  -我们温和的敦促他
Well... Yeah.   -Well, we were pushing him, gently
开出我们要的价钱 结果他他妈的
on what we wanted, how much, and then he fuckin'
怎么形容呢  -我会说 他大暴走
How would you describe it like?   -I would describe it
人形版的 切尔诺贝利核灾  -对 没错
as a meltdown, human Chernobyl.   -Yeah. Right
但 具体而言 他是…
But, like, specifically.
具体而言 他大孔道
Specifically, he was, like, shouting about how
我们不知道什么叫好的交易
you know, we didn't know what a good deal was,
还有 他并不是很想做这笔生意
and how he didn't even especially want the deal.
他不想做这笔生意吗
He didn't want the deal?
对 是他的资深管理团想做
Yeah, like, his senior leadership team, liked it
叫我们最好接受他开的条件
but, you know, we better take what was on the table
我觉得 这像是谈判策略
But that... That smells like a negotiating tactic to me,
因为价是他自己开的  -也许是
'cause he made the offer.   -I mean, may be.
他说的话没什么条理 他的意思大概是
It wasn't really coherent. He was sort of, like
他在耍我们
saying that he was stringing us along
也随时可以反悔 然后...
and that he could, you know, pull the deal and.
所以呢 你们有什么想法
So, what are you suggesting?
我们可以推荐跟这种性格的人交易吗
Can we recommend a deal with a person of this character?
毕竟这个人的问题很多 像是乱发推文 嗑药的传闻
Given everything else and so on? Tweet s, drug rumors.
你知道50%的换股 这表示我们风险很高
You know, 50 percent in stock, that means we are exposed.
我可以说吗 没错 这确实让人担心
Shall I go? Okay, it's a worry.
这是个问题 我觉得我们得密切观察
It's, a concern and I think we should monitor it closely
但我觉得 没什么大碍
I don't think it hurts
他是个天才
I mean, he's, a genius
大家不会介意天才举止怪异
Nobody minds a genius acting weird.
说真的 这也许会让他更有神秘色彩
Honestly, it probably kind of adds to the mystique.
而且 我们知道 目前
And we know that his bank
他的银行和法律团
and legal team are, right now.
正以非常专业的态度处理此事
progressing in a very professional manner
有什么好担心的
I just... What... what's... What's to worry? It's..
我们定价时 已经考量了他的名声  -没错
His reputation is priced in.   -Absolutely
很好 行 好 那我们就放心了
Good. Yeah, okay, we feel covered
当然 是  -对吧 我们就是…
Sure. Yeah.   -Right? Just... Just
想让各位知道这事 然后
letting you guys know and, we should..
我们该继续推进了
we should move ahead with what we know
谢谢你们告诉我们
Thank you for keeping us informed.
谢谢各位
Thanks, guys.
谢了弗兰克
Thanks, Frank.
明天是大日子 重要的产品发布会
Big day tomorrow. Big product launch.
嗨
HI
我们...抱歉 没先跟你说
We... Sorry, we didn't mention
我们不想节外生枝
We... We were just... We're hoping to keep things dry
行吧 是吗
Yeah. Yeah?
对  -对
Yeah.   -Yeah.
我们是因为虚荣心而没说吧 也许是
I think vanity stopped us, maybe.
我们因之前谈到高价而自豪 所以...
We were proud of the deal, from raising it earlier. So..
对 当然了
Yeah. Sure.
怎么了 我了解你们
What?   -I know you.
怎样了.  -我太他妈了解你们了
What?   -I fucking know you
怎么了  -怎么了?
What?   -" What "?
对啊 怎么了  -“怎么了?”
Yeah, what?   -" What?"
怎么了  -真他妈要命
What?   -I Fucking hell.
小子们 你们演技太差了
Boys, you're not good at this
爸 小西把巧克力牛奶
Hey, Dad? Shiv spilled chocolate milk
洒到路虎上了
in the Range Rover."
对吧
Yeah?
你们想故意搞砸这笔交易  -才没有
You're trying to fuck the deal.   -No, we're not
没有吗  -我们没有想要故意搞砸交易
No? Yeah?   -No, we're not trying to fuck the deal.
但你们居然没跟我提过
But you failed to mention this very
这有趣的小插曲 连八卦的时候都没提
fucking interesting incident, even as a bit of gossip?
小西
Shiv..
怎么  -不是的
Yeah?   -No.
不是吗 我错了吗
No? I'm wrong?
来 说谎吧 当着我的面撒谎
Go on, lie to me. Lie to my face
我们不太确定 想不想卖
We're not sure about the deal
谢了 混球 太好了
Thanks, fuck face. Excellent
我就是...  -行吧 不 很好
Just, what am I...   -Yeah. I mean, no, great.
就让我背黑... 太好了 漂亮
Throw me under the fuckin'... Great. Nice.
小西 我们本来打算告诉你
Shiv, I mean, the plan was to tell you. We were..
说真的 我们是在保护你
Honestly, we were protecting you.
太感谢了
Thanks so much
是啊 我的纯洁天真可不容钻污
Yeah, don't get mud on my confirmation dress.
太他妈感谢你们了
Thanks so fucking much.
当时在山上的情况 确实是失控了 小西
Well, it did go nuts on the mountain, Shiv
他说爸爸的坏话 我们的计划一直是…
He was talking shit about Dad.   -The plan was always
干净利落的脱身.....  -对
we were getting out clean...   -Yeah
经营皮尔斯 一起买下皮尔斯
Doing Pierce, buying Pierce together.
怎么回事啊
What the fuck happened?
小西 也许我们可以留下韦斯达和皮尔斯 我们三个
Shiv, maybe we can keep it, and Pierce, all of us.
天啊 你们俩狗东西
Man, you are fucking cocksuckers
小西 我们...我...
Shiv, we're... I'm...
我们真的很抱歉 真的
Sor... I mean, we're sorry. We are
我们不想骗你的
We wouldn't have dicked you over
行
Yeah.
我们不想让你趟浑水
We wanted to keep you clean
我们该不该...
Should we like..
要不要抱一下
Can we do the huggy thing?
好啊  -是吗
Sure.   -Yeah?
好  -好了 我很抱歉
Yeah.  -All right. I am sorry.
抱歉
Sorry.
没事了吧
Cool?
对不起
Sorry.
你好  -我...
Hello.   -I have a..
怎么了  -我约了人 不能改期
What?   -...appointment that I can't reschedule
所以.....好 没问题
So... Okay. Sure.
帮你预约了这间  -都准备好了吗
You're in here.   -We all set?
应该是 二十分钟后讨论投资人关系
Think so. Investor relations in 20?
好 谢了
Yeah. Thanks
你想给我什么  -我想给你...
What do you wanna give me?   -I wanna give you..
混蛋 快说  -小小看一下今晚的选择
Douche. What?   -A little preview of tonight's selection.
嘿 嘿  -嘿
Hey. Hey.   -  -Hey...
去吧  -抱歉
Go on.   -Sorry.
你还好吗
All right. You okay?
我很好
I'm fine.
我订了这个会议室
We had... We had this room booked
没问题 我马上走
Okay. Right. No, I'll leave you to it.
我以为这里...没人用
I thought the room was... empty for...
你真的没事吗  -对 我很好
You really okay?   -Yeah, fine
确定
You sure?
对 我只是很忙
Yes. I'm just very busy
然后...
And...
爸爸的事情 让我忙到不行
I have found I am too busy, what with my dad
所以 莎拉有时候会帮我找个地方
And so, Sarah has sometimes found me somewhere
让我有时间哭一下
so that I can... have a moment to cry
对  -你安排时间让自己哀悼吗
Yeah.   -You're scheduling your grief?
你...滚出去行吗
Just... just fuck off. Yeah?
没事的 小西
Hey. Come on. Shiv.
没事的
Come on.
没事的 没关系 没关系
Come on. It's okay. It's okay
没关系
It's okay.
很可惜 我儿子肯德尔和罗曼·罗伊
" Sadly, my sons, Kendall and Roman Roy
忙着处理重要的公事
are too tied up with important company business
没办法出席今年的投资日
to join us at this year's Investment Day.
这段不留吗
We're not gonna keep that in?
留下来吧
Let's keep that in.
一人一句会不会很可笑
Does it feel cheesy to alternate
还是应该一人念一段
or... or should we do block one, block two?
没事的 都可以
No, it's fine. It's whatever. It's... Yeah
你觉得...谢谢
What do you think on... Thank you
你觉得马特森该怎么办
What do you think on Mats son?
如果香果圈行动失败的话
If you know, Operation Fruit Loop doesn't fly
召集股东
Muster a share bloc?
说服董事会 他只会摧毁价值
Board, convince he's a value destroyer?
说有法规问题 希望价钱告吹
Regulatory shit? Hope the price runs away?
我也不知道 总之得找个借口
I don't know. Something.
泰利斯说 他最高只能出到192
Tell is says he doesn't have juice past 192
这件事让我很消沉
Well, something about this all does depress me.
是吗 是因为这篇
Yeah? And, do you think it's the speech
为我们亡父量身打造的讲稿
written specifically for our late father,
还是 因为我们打算把老家伙们关起来
or the fact we're planning to warehouse the elderly
用内容让他们迷醉 再趁机吸光他们的钱
and keep them drunk on content while we suck'em dollar dry?
我想 是90年代的企划
I think it's the'90s pitch
个人化的长寿计划
" Personalized longevity programs.
我看到了 那是什么
I see them.   -What is that?
有这种东西吗
Is that something?
能让我们看看草稿吗 杰西  -好
Can we see drafts, J?   -Yeah
双击长寿
Give me the double click on longevity
让我看到全部 就像无限大脑益智盒
so I can see everything. Infinite brainbox
好
Yeah.
我可以问乔伊·帕玛
I can, ask Joy Palmer if the fucking
卡利·斯派特隆的导演能不能来帮忙
Kali spit ron director can come on board
把视频拍得混乱又大声
and make everything more confusing and loud
是现在吗 乔伊  -对 是现在
Is that... is that now? Joy?   -Yeah. That's now.
好 去施展魔力
All right, sprinkle some sugar.
好 会的  -要有信心 好吗
Yeah. Will do.   -Full confidence. Yeah?
速度要加快点 老弟
Gotta up our velocity, man.
对 连她都能拍出一部卖座大片
Yeah. I mean, even she should be able to come up with a mega  -hit
只要多给两张内容单
from a couple extra content bill.
打破倡局 让这个系列动起来
Just break the log jam, get the franchise pump pumping
好吗 给点劲  -给点劲 对 太他妈对了
Yeah? Pump it up.   -Pump it. Yeah. Fuck yeah
我会拼命给那个自大的婊子灌迷汤
I'm gonna love-bomb that stuck-up bitch.
好 一杆进洞 一飞冲天吧 罗曼
All right. Shoot it to the moon, Rome
没问题  -新的太空牛仔来了
Will do.   -New space cowboys in town.
没错 谁想干 我已经准备好 可以干了
Yeah. Who wants to fuck? I'm ready to fuck
谁准备好要大于一场了
Who ready for Fucky wood?
你好  -罗曼·罗伊
Hello.   -Roman Roy.
是我  -嘿
'Tis I.   -Hey.
你好吗 很高兴见到你
How are you? Good to see you.
我们要致上最诚挚的慰问之意
We'd all like to offer our sincere condolences
谢谢 你真好
Thank you. That's... That's very nice.
是的  -但我拒绝
Yes.   -Refused.
慰问我的人 已经够多了
I have all the condolences I need.
不想再被人慰问 开始吧
Tummy full. Shall we?
你只是还没有反应过来
Well, it just hasn't hit you yet
不是的 这...  -一定会的
No. It's...   -You know, I'm sure it will
但你不会有事的 这需要时间
But you'll be okay. It takes time.
太谢谢你了 真的非常感谢
Okay. Well, many, many thanks. Many, many, many, many, many.
你不会有事的  -好的
You'll be fine.   -Okay
交易的事 让人很兴奋
And it's very exciting about the deal
他是什么样子
What's he like?
卢卡斯吗 他很好 很古怪 像嗑了药 注意力涣散
Lukas? Great. Flaky. Really druggy, odd, not focused.
但你知道的 老实说 他有一些问题
But, yeah. You know. Honestly, few issues.
我可以搞定 但是...
I'm sure I can fix it, but..
我坐不住 我有一些想法
So, I can't stand still. I.. I have thoughts
当然 大家都有
Well, of course. Everybody does.
你说什么  -我在学格劳乔·马克思
What was that?   -A little Groucho Marx for ya
这样哦 是是是
Right. Yeah, yeah, yeah.
电影内幕  -是的 我就是想
Inside cinema.   -Yeah, so I just sort a
先把话说开 “卡利·斯派特隆”
wanted to may be just get it out of the way. Kali spitron?
我只想知道 谁会为了这部烂片而被开除
I just wanna know who's getting fired for that shit show.
我当然可以随时跟你报告 但情况很复杂
I mean, I can certainly loop you in, but it's complicated.
好吧
Okay.
可以私下讨论吗 你知道的...
Shall we just sidebar that? You know, that..
因为这个问题很敏感
particular situation has lots of big personalities
很敏感
Big personalities
是的 这可绝对不能再发生
Yeah, I can't see that happening again.
放心 我很重视这个问题
No, I've been taking it very seriously
很好 好的 是这样 我
Good. Okay. Well... Look, I... I... I'm..
我会帮你争取到经费 好吗
I'm gonna turn on the money hose for you. Okay?
我们想支持你 但我们只想听到你说
We wanna back you. We just wanna hear
有信心能拍出一部卖座片
that you're confident that we can the hit machine pump in'
那当然 是的
Well, absolutely. Yeah
不过 有一件事 让我们有点担心
I mean, there is one thing that we have been concerned about
好 说来听听 我准备好了
Okay. Hit me. I'm ready.
来解决吧
Let's do it.
泛美网科的右翼倾向...
The right ward lean from ATN.
很多人担心民主党的机构
Lots of people are concerned about democratic institutions.
是 是 我知道了
Yeah. Yeah. Got it.
你要我说更多
You want me to say more things.
很多人向我们问起 泛美网科对门肯的
We're getting a lot of questions about A TN's favorable coverage
偏颇报道
on Mencken.
我想说 你有没有办法
I mean, isn't there something you can do
跟他保持距离  -是 是 听我说
to signal a distance?   -Yeah, yeah. Look.
门肯也是一部作品 就如别的节目
Mencken's IP. just like anything. Yeah?
我不喜欢他 你也不喜欢他 但又能怎么办呢
I don't like him, you don't like him. What are we gonna do?
但 我现在讲的是人才
But it's all in terms of talent. You know?
公司...
The company..
我们在这个创意社群中是有价值的
We have values here in this creative community
我知道 我懂 我很欣赏你们的价值
And I know, I get it. And I... And I love the values.
你在这个断层带上
I mean, it's, an incredibly evolved
打造了一个高度进化
ruthlessly segregated city
和残酷隔离的城市
you built on this geological fault here.
咱们就别自欺欺人了  -我们也在努力
Let's get real.   -Look, we're trying.
我总觉得...是的 我觉得
I just... I sort of feel like... Yeah, I feel like..
你没有把我的话听进去
you're not really listening to me?
我刚刚说 我要给你很多钱
I'm saying I'm gonna just dump a ton of money on you
只希望你能拍出一部卖座大片
and all we want is to get the hit pump pump in'
你听懂了吧
You understand, right?
平衡流媒体 和剧院放映
Balance between streaming and theatrical.
打造一个系列国际营销 好吗
Franchise creation. International marketing. Yeah?
好 你可以交给我 我明白 很令人兴奋
Yeah, you can trust me. I got it. Very exciting.
好
All right.
你知道吗
You know...
乔伊 我明白 你在想
Joy. I, I get it. I... You're thinking
这家伙懂什么
" The fuck does this guy know about anything?
他又不是他爸 他做不到的
He's not his dad. He can't do it
罗曼过去的纪录烂透了
Roman's track record is bullshit.
不 我相信你能坐上这个位子
No, I'm sure you are where you are
是有原因的
for very good reason
我可以直接开除你 所以…
I could just fire you. So...
你觉得很好笑吗 我真的可以
That's a funny joke? I could
听我说 我认为...  -我不是说会开除你
Look, I... I think...   -I'm not saying I am.
只是说 我可以
I'm just saying I could.
也许我该开除你  -不
Although may be I should.   -No.
糟糕 我说出口了 既然说出来 就要做到
No, I said it. Now I feel like I gotta commit
我们的财务业绩已经完全失控
Our tent pole is bullshit and out of control,
你救不了的 所以 我决定了
and you're not gonna fix it, so I'm calling it
对不起 到此为止  -你…
I'm sorry. We're done.   -Are..
是的 我们…  -你是不是
Yeah, we're... we're...   -Are you
这 对的 我想说的是
This is... Yeah, I am. What I mean to say is the,
公司想解雇你
the... the company wishes to terminate your employment
人事部会跟你联络 开始办离职手续
HR will be in touch to start the termination process.
祝你未来一切顺利
We wish you the best of luck on all your future endeavors.
你这样做 大错特错了
This is a mistake.
好吧
Okay.
嘿 洁德  -怎么了
Hey, Jade...   -Yes?
能不能…
Can... can we get.
叫拉娜和雨果 再看一次确认的分析师
Let's get Lana and Hugo on analyst double check, who's confirmed
叫拉吉问一次容易回答的问题
And let's get Raj primed to throw some softballs. Okay?
小西可以说这些
And I think Shiv can just say
也许再说这个
you know, this and this, and... and may be... maybe this
交给罗曼 通知他们一声 好吗
Give that to Roman. Just let'em know. Okay?
好 我会告诉他们
Yeah. I can let them know.
至于提示灯方面 我们得跟库希
And in terms of lighting cues, just so we can brief Kush
和影视团队简报 你有什么想法
and the AV team. What are you thinking
肯...
Ken...
可以帮我建造一栋 生活+的房子吗
Could we build me a Living Plus house?
你是说…
As in...
小小的 用夹板 最基本的砌砖 不用太夸张
Small, plywood, basic brickwork, nothing crazy
我可以穿过那栋房子
I could walk through it.
这里播放泛美网科 脸部老化投射在这边的墙壁上
ATN on here. Face aging on the wall here.
也许房子上方还有云朵 你觉得呢
May be clouds appear above the house. What do you think?
我们可以问问美工团队 丹尼
We can definitely check with the team. Denny?
你的想法很有意思 但是...
It... it's certainly an exciting vision, but..
别说不行 丹尼
Don't say no, Denny.
明天要用的吗
This is for tomorrow?
好莱坞就是这样 对吧
Hollywood though. Right?
我们需要一栋房子 实际建造
We need a house, practical build.
我有一条规定 好吗 谁都不能说”不行”
Here's the rule. Okay? No one can say no.
好的肯德尔 谢谢肯德尔
" Yes, Kendall. Thank you, Kendall
谢谢你订了这么酷的规定
for the cool new rule.
谢谢肯德尔  -谢谢肯德尔
Thank you, Kendall.   -Thank'you, Kendall
谢谢肯德尔  -谢谢你订了这么酷的规定
Thank you, Kendall.   -For the cool new rule.
嘿
Hey!
打气还顺利吗
Good pep talk?
是的 很顺利 充满欢乐
Yeah, good, good, full of joy.
但 后来变得
It kind of turned into
我待会儿再跟你说  -好 是这样
Whatever, I'll catch you up in a bit.   -Okay, look
我刚刚在看发布会的东西
I've been looking through the launch deck
我想到一个
I have a big..
一个很重要的点子
I have a... I have a big thought
一旦产品发布 而且没有默认立场
It's looking great. Without an investor relation to withhold.
可以失陪一下吗 谢谢
Would you excuse me for a moment? Thank you
嘿
Hey
嗨  -嘿
Hi.   -Hey.
在享受投资人酒会吗
Enjoying the investor reception?
抱歉 我不想害你束手束脚
Sorry, I don't wanna cramp your style.
不不不
No, no, no.
你一定很想扑上去
I'm sure you're keen to get amongst it.
扑上去?
" It "?
对 扑到那些身高不够高
Yeah, the... the vaginas of the cheerful women
当不了模特的欢乐女子的下体上
who aren't tall enough to be models
不 不用了 不用了
Nah, I'm good. I'm good.
好
Okay.
那...你喜欢谁
So... Who do you like?
我可以猜一下吗
Yeah? Can I guess?
她不错
Could do.
原来你就是晃来晃去
Is that what you've been doing, going around and just, like
找人说话吗 那些长腿金发妹吗
saying things to people? The leggy blondes?
和肤色健康的模特  -你知道…
The tan models.   -You know..
靠过去 说 “嗨 嘿 我是汤姆”
Like, leaning in, saying, " Hi. Hey, I'm Tom."
我本来 想说几句真心话
I think, I guess, if I was gonna say something
本来想说 我很抱歉
from the heart, I would say I'm sorry
你很抱歉?  -对 我很抱歉
You're sorry?   -Yeah, I'm sorry
抱歉让你伤得那么重
I'm sorry for fucking you up.
想得美
You should be so lucky.
你差得远了
You hardly scratched the surface.
早在认识你之前 我就已经受伤了
I was fucked up long before I met you
怎么 因为TK吗
What, with TK?
对 因为TK 还有华盛顿的事
Yeah. Yeah, with TK. The Washington situation.
你只是在那个人之后出现的人
You were the one after the one.
我说的是我最爱的男人 他总是…
The actual one, and that's always.
跟在他后面很不容易
You know, that's hard.
我觉得 多少造成了一点伤害
I think I got my chisel in on you.
连刮伤都不算
Hardly a scratch
但 你嘛 我是你全部的故事
But you, I mean, I'm the whole story for you.
我扭碎了你的心
I just twisted your heart right up
对 大概吧
Yeah, I guess.
玛丽? 汤姆 少来了 我把你整惨了
Mary? Tom, please. I did a number on you
玛丽? 我认识你之前
Mary? You didn't have... You didn't have a taste
你根本对黑人没兴趣
of the dark meat before you met me.
我本来也可以浪荡情场的
I'd had my times.
想不想玩咬人游戏?
You want to play bitey?
“咬人游戏?"  -你没玩过咬人游戏吗
Bitey?   -We never played bitey?
没有
No
就是你咬我一口
Okay, well, you bite me.
我咬你一口 看谁忍得住
I bite you, see who can take it.
好啊 当然  -手臂伸出来
Okay, sure.   -Give me your arm.
先停的人就输了
So, first one to stop, loses.
咬人游戏
Bitey.
咬人游戏 准备好了吗  -大概吧
Bitey. Ready?   -Yeah, I guess
你只有这点力气吗
Is that all you got?
要死
Motherfucker
咬人游戏
Bitey!
你还好吗
You okay?
没事 汤姆·威姆士丹终于让我有感觉了
Yeah. Tom Wambsgans finally made me feel something
真会说
Nice.
我看了资料 想到一个企划
So, I've been through the material and I have a pitch
是吗
Okay.
不可思议的成长
Unbelievable growth.
价格狂飙  -好的
Price rocket.   -Okay
只要把价格往上推 交易就注定破局
Drive the price, we make the deal impossible
所以 你只需要不可思议的成长
So all you need is unbelievable growth?
好吧 讽刺博士 我有叫你讲话吗
Okay, all right, Dr.Sarcasmo. Did we ask you to squeak?
好好当你的人形立牌  -如果能冲破192
Stand easy there, pitch wall.   -If we can drive above 192
没人觉得马特森出得起
no one thinks Mats son has the juice
好吧 所以…  -他只能放手
Okay, so...   -He has to walk
用价格逼他走人吗
Chase him out on price?
我想 这样的地产计划
I think we can get a tech valuation
可以做科技评估
for a real estate proposition on this
生活+吗
Living Plus?
好吧...我觉得
Well... Can I just say.
很难把房子归为科技类
I... I think it's hard to make houses seem like tech
因为 房子问世已经一段时间了
cause we've had houses for a while now.
我们需要 分析师以不同的角度 看我们公司
Just, we need to make analysts look at the company differently
跟你说 这个就是必杀应用程序
I'm telling you, this is the killer app.
将你的体能潜力发挥得淋漓尽致
Maximize your physical potential
长...不是长生不老啦
live... well, not... Not forever...
为什么不是长生不老   -当然 如果不是长生不老
Why not forever?   -Well, sure. If not forever.
就说更能长命百岁
live more forever.
人形立牌酷不酷
Pitch bot, is it dope?
蛮酷的 麻烦学机器人讲话 人形立牌
It's kind a dope. Like a robot, please, pitch bot
蛮酷的
It's kind of dope.
天啊 你被开除了
My God, you're fired.
我们可以把这个顶上天
We can push this to the moon.
但我们还没有数字 对吧
But we don't have the numbers, right?
这些不...这些数字是白的,  -新数字会出来的
These are not... These are the old numbers.   -We'll have the numbers
会吗   -会
We'll have the numbers?   -Yeah.
那...我们的绝招是什么
So then, what... where... where's our go  -to?
我想甜蜜点
I guess the sweet spot would be
是介于超他妈美味
right after they get fucking delicious
及超他妈愚蠢之间
and just before they get fucking stupid
对  -对吧
Right.   -Right?
格雷格 去找杰西 还有 照我说的去
Greg, go find Jess, and what we talked about,
剪辑  -机器人退场
getting the edit.   -Robot out
滚啦
Beat it, scrub.
跟你说 我喜欢
You know, I like it.
我是不太喜欢死亡 所以...
I mean, I'm not crazy myself about dying. So
我知道 是不是 这是狗屁
I know, right? It's bullshit
有点不... 这很...
It was kind of not... It was very..
那个不是
I just, you know.
我没想到 爸会突然过世
It wasn't... I just didn't see it coming with Dad
是啊  -是啊
Yeah.   -Yeah
完全不像爸的作风  -没错
It's very un-Dad.   -Very un-Dad
如果有另一条路可以走
So I think people would be very intrigued
我想人们会很有兴趣的
if there was another way through the whole situation.
你是说人生吗  -人生
You mean life?   -Life
对 对   -还有死亡 对
Yeah. Yeah.   -  -Death, yeah.
你知道的 上传到芯片 然后
Yeah, yeah. I mean, you know, get loaded onto a chip and
射进某人的屁眼
fired up someone's ass,
像气体般飘浮 但是变成乌龟
float around as a gas, live in a tortoise,
我也不知道 死亡一定有很多不同的形式
I don't know. There's got to be ways through
这样感觉太千篇一律了
Death just feels very "one size fits all.
对 对 对
Yeah, yeah, yeah
罗曼  -怎么了
Roman.   -Yeah
我有话跟你说  -格丽 我想... 好
I want to talk to you.   -Gerri. I want to... Okay
那是什么鬼
The fuck is that?
我很忙 怎么回事
I'm on a schedule. So, what is this?
怎么了
What happened?
什么怎么了  -乔伊?
With what?   -With Joy?
她不接电话
She's not picking up.
还找了外部的律师  -对
She's got outside counsel?   -Yeah.
到底是怎么回事  -我把她开除了 所以呢
What the fuck happened?   -Look, I fired her. So?
罗曼 你开除电影公司主管之前
Roman, you absolutely can not fire a studio executive
要先问过法务和人事
without speaking to Legal and HR
现场还要 有别人在场
and... and, having someone else present,
免得...  -对对 不过我可以 因为我已经做了
in case...   -Right, right, except I can because I did.
你究竟跟她说了什么
What precisely did you say?
因为 现在我们可能挨告  -谁在乎
Because now we are open to litigation... Who cares?
成为笑柄…
And ridicule...
还得想想 要怎么道歉
and now, we have to think of how to frame an apology
或者改口...  -我的老天爷啊 我没开除她 好吗
or row back...   -Jesus fucking Christ, I didn't fire her. Okay?
我只是跟她说 她被开除了 如此而已
I said that she was fired to her, that's all
那是什么意思
The fuck does that mean?
意思是 她不会流落街头 好吗
It means she's not going to be on the fucking street. Okay?
我们会让她去负责国际部
We'll kick her up to International,
或是 离职之后去当制片 领高薪
or she walks and takes a fat fucking producer deal
你可以负责收拾善后 好吗 动作快
You can work on the sweep up, okay? Chop-chop.
乔伊很有人脉 她的朋友很多
Joy has a lot of relationships. She has a lot of friends
我也是 怎样  -你是处于危险过渡期的
So do I.   -And you are weak monarch
软弱君主  -才不是
in a dangerous interregnum.   -No, no.
我觉得 你必须重新考虑
And I think you need to reconsider
我爸也会这么做的
This is something that Dad would have done,
你心里明白  -也许吧 但你不是你爸
and you know it.   -Well, maybe. But you're not your dad
好吧 好吧
Okay. Okay.
你的处境比较复杂 好吗  -好 我是不成才的接班人
I mean, you're in a more complicated position, okay?   -No, I'm what's left.
格丽 是这样的
Gerri, here's the fucking thing.
怎样  -我开会一半 被你拖出来
What?   -You hauling me out of things
你让我重新考虑正确的决定
telling me to reconsider good calls,
还对我 爆粗口
and using the F-word freely
感觉…很不尊重我
it... it feels... it feels disrespectful.
我需要你相信
I need you...
我跟我爸一样厉害
to believe that I am as good as my dad
你做得到吗
Can you do that?
你是要我说 还是要我真心相信?
Say it or believe it?
你对我不够尊重
You don't treat me with sufficient respect,
这是个问题
and that's a problem
也许我该连你一起开除
Well, maybe I'll fire you, too.
最好是 我不在狙杀名单上  -所以呢
Sure, I'm not on the kill list.   -So?
所以 马特森会很生气  -马特森可以去死 我才不管
So, Mats son will be very angry.   -Fuck Mats son, I don't care.
别闹了 你只是在看家
Be serious, you're minding shop
罗曼 不不不不 罗曼
Roman. No, no, no, no. Roman?
怎么  -跟金钱对抗 你是赢不了的
Yeah.   -You can not win against the money
金钱会让你粉身碎骨 你爸就很清楚
The money is gonna wash you away. Your dad knew.
科技人员要来了 我们玩完了
Tech is coming. We are over
跟董事会建议吧 好吗  -这是个很单纯的商业决策
Make your accommodation. Okay.   -This is a simple business decision.
你的工作能力不好 也许爸已经知道了
You are not good at your job. May be Dad did know.
也许我开除你 是因为
May be I'm firing you for a list of failures
一长串我现在不想提的失败
I choose not to outline right now.
也许包括了
but including a failure to close of f our liabilities
面对韦斯达邮轮时
vis-a-vis claims against Way star Cruises
没能及时止损
in a timely manner.
感觉顺理成章 就这么说吧
That'll play nicely. Let's do that.
我的工作能力很强  -要开始准备
I am good at my job.   -Shall we get started
离职文件了吗 你要自己处理
on the paperwork? You wanna do it yourself,
还是要我找个比较灵光的人
or do you want me to get somebody a bit sharper?
再见
Bye!
该死的混账
You fucking ass hole!
我想我们可以往上推 往上推 往上推
Yeah. I think we can push. Push it, push it.
嘿 罗曼 这太棒了  -是吗
Hey. This is juicy as fuck, Rome.   -Yeah?
今晚要挑灯夜战了
We're gonna work through the night.
酷  -是啊
Cool.   -Yeah
嘿 你可以去酒会露个脸吗
Hey, and, you okay to show face at the reception?
你是说那个派对吗 没问题  -就是那件事情之后
The party? Sure.   -After the thing?
好  -因为我得紧紧盯着
Okay.   -Because I got the big eye on.
看样子 越来越有搞头了 兄弟  -很好
The ball is looking fat, bro.   -Good
我什么都看到了  -很好 很好 很好
I can see everything.   -Good, good, good
我想跟你说一声
So, it's just... I think you should know.
我觉得 我们应该开除乔伊
I think we should let Joy go.
是吗  -是 是
Okay. Yeah?   -Yeah. Yeah.
现在 就是要让外界觉得 我们有所作为
I mean, right now, it's kind of all about the move, so that's.
我觉得 这样很好
Yeah, that's... that's... Dude, that's baller for me
是吗 好极了  -对 对 来终结乔伊吧
Yeah? Great.   -Yeah. yeah. Let's put an end to Joy
很好  -杀了乔伊
Great.   -Death to Joy
格丽说 这样不好
Gerri told me that that was a bad move
叫我收回成命
and I should sort a roll that back
所以 我开除了格丽
so I, I fired Gerri.
滚蛋吧 你开除了格丽? 小西的教母 格丽?
Fuck off. You fired Gerri? Shiv's godmother, Gerri?
对 但我们可能要收回成命
Yeah. Yeah, but we may need to roll back on that
你可能得去安抚她一下
I don't know, you may need to smooth over, whatever
别管了 老弟 有何不可 就把她扫地出门吧
Fuck it, bro. Why not? Drop her in the end zone.
瞧瞧你
I mean, look at you
你接下来要开除谁
Who... Who are you gonna fire next?
开除弗兰克
I mean, fire Frank
开除卡尔 吃掉格雷格 连我也开除
fire Karl, fucking eat Greg, and fire me, man.
我不知道 这很严重  -你现在火力全开
Yeah, I don't know, it's big.   -You're on fire.
这很严重 这感觉很严重  -不 这不严重 这不严重
It feels big. It feels maybe it's a bit big.   -No, it's not big. It's not big
这不严重吗  -要用爸的方式思考 对吧 没什么的
It's not too big? Yeah?   -Put on the Dad goggles. Right? It's nothing
是吗   -没什么 “韦斯达活力二人组…
Yeah?   -Nothing. " Dynamic Way star duo
整顿垂垂老矣的管理团队”
shake up their senior leadership team."
接下来 引述一些人的抱怨 重点来了
Grumble quote, grumble quote, caveat
有些人说 这两个年轻人也许
" Some are saying these two young turks
能扭转局面
might just have what it takes to turn things around.'
不错吧
Nice?
很不错
Very nice.
你对 大选派对 有什么想法
Hey, what do you think about the election party?
你爸爸的派对 我可以当主持人吗
Your dad's party? You think maybe I should host?
谁打来的 进攻的维京人吗
Who's that? Striking Viking?
对
Yeah.
我问你一件事
Let me ask you one thing
你赞成卖给马特森吗
You're all in on Mats son?
对 应该吧
Yeah. I guess
你两个哥哥讨厌我 你也讨厌我
I mean, your brothers hate me, and you hate me
你们会开除我所以我赞成
and you'll fire me. So, yeah
我有点
I don't entirely.
不确定该怎么处理
entirely know what to do
你是说马特森吗
Regarding Mats son?
对 我们处得很好 所以...
Yeah. Well, you know, we have a connection. So..
你们处得很好吗
You have a connection?
对 怎么了
Yeah. What?
怎么了 只是 不...
What? It's just not, like..
你想拍他马屁
Because you want to suck him off
不表示 我也一定得想上他
you think that... That I must want to fuck him?
觉得我们会一起住在马特森的豪宅里
Think we're all gonna live together in a big old Mats son house.
滥交狂欢 唱着马特森的歌吗
you know, fucking each other and singing Mats son songs?
你还是一个选项都不放过 亲爱的
Still keeping all your options open, honey?
是吗 你最好小心一点
Yeah? You should be careful with that
假面男 突然说实话了
Truth bombs from... t from the phony man.
我觉得...我想要你 我想重拾旧情
I think... I think I want you. I think I would like this back
那你就不该背叛我
Well then, you shouldn't have betrayed me.
假面男
Phony.
如果我要说实话 事实是
If I try to say it. If I try to say the truth.
我认识你的时候 我这辈子
It's that when I met you, all my life..
一直在想钱的事...
I've been thinking a little bit about money..
想着怎么赚钱 怎么把钱留在身边
and how to get money, and how to keep money
而你 没有接纳我
And you didn't ask me in.
小西 你把我拒之门外
Shiv, you kept me out.
我一直配合 你公私分明的作风
And I always agreed to all the compartments,
但我觉得 一定会在你和你爸之间
but it seemed to me that I was gonna be caught
左右为难
between you and your dad.
我非常热爱我的事业
And I really, really, really love my career
和我的钱
and my money.
你知道的 还有我的西装 和名表 和...
And, you know, the suits, and my watches, and..
对 我知道
Yeah. Sure, I know.
我喜欢好东西 真的
I like nice things, I do
如果你觉得我肤浅
And if you think that's shallow.
何不为了爱 放弃你所有的东西
why don't you throw out all your stuff for love.
放弃你的项链和珠宝
Throw out your necklaces and your jewels
只为在三星意大利餐厅约会
for a date at a three-star Italian
可以吗 来跟我一起住拖车公园
Yeah? Come and live with me in a trailer park
可以吗 你来不来
Yeah? Are you coming?
我会为了爱 跟你走天涯的 汤姆·威姆士丹
Well, I'd follow you anywhere for love, Tom Wambsgans.
我相信
I'm convinced
我们的”生活+”房地产品牌
that the Living Plus real estate brand
可以让邮轮体验正式登陆
can bring the cruise ship experience to dry land
并为我们的乐园部门
and provide a significant boost to the earnings
带来丰厚进账  -好 可以停了
of our parks division.   -Okay, you can... You can stop it. So, that's.
我们要他说的是 带来双倍进账
So, what we want him to say... We want him to say
而不是丰厚进账
"double the earnings " instead of "a significant boost."
我不确定
Well, I, I'm not sure
这是否做得到
that I can do that.
但我敢说 你可以
But I bet you can.
我可以跟音效剪辑师谈
Yeah. I can talk to the sound editor but
但 若没有他说这几个字的视频...
you know, without those words, without him saying...
你可以用其他的片段剪辑
No, yeah. You... you... you can build it from other bits
这个嘛  -就是...
Well.   -In... in the..
我不知道可不可以
Yeah, I don't know if I can.
当然可以 我需要你这么做
Well, yeah, you can. I need you to
我是说 从技术上来说
Well, I mean it's just that, technically
我不确定做得到
I don't think that I can do that
不 听着... 够了...
No, no. Look... That... that's enough
够了 好吗 这...
That's enough. Okay? That just.
总之 想办法做到就是了
Just fuckin' make it happen.
一定要做到 好吗   -好
Make it happen. Okay?   -Okay
不然我会有麻烦 我不希望有麻烦
Or I get in trouble. And I don't wanna get in trouble
我想上白名单
I wanna get in the good books
帮我上白名单
So, you help me get in the good books
懂了吗 剪辑师先生
Understand, Mr. Snippy-snip?
如果加倍呢
What if we doubled that?
这是什么意思
What is that?
我觉得你比我更清楚...  -可以加倍吗
Well, I think you know the specific...   -Can we double it?
你比我更清楚这个行业
You know the specific business better than me,
但是 以单位而言 如果乐观点
but on units, if we go optimistic...
来个爆炸性的乐观吧 彼得
Go explosive, Pete.
可能吧 第一波会是佛罗里达
I guess, the first wave being Florida
科罗拉多 亚利桑那 500   -能不能上修到一千
Colorado, Arizona, 500.   -Could that be 1,000?
应该可以 是的  -再来是
I suppose. Yeah.   -And then the,
五年和十年期预测
five and ten-year projections?
数字一定要非常可信
I mean, it needs to be super credible
彼得 一定要有可信度
Pete, it's gotta be credible.
新产品和服务
New products and services
营销的机器学习
machine learning on the marketing
加上 重新包装给第三方的 健康资讯
plus repackaging health data to third parties.
每个月 轻轻松松 就能成长...
Easily, easily grow that.
我...  -两到三个百分点
I...   -Two, three percent per month
这样 复合年均成长率是多少
What... what does that... what does that do to CAGR?
会不会变多 彼得
Does it make it bigger, Pete?
会多很多  -多多少 百分之五十每年吗
It makes it a lot bigger.   -What? Fifty percent? Per year?
还是 五年进账会变十倍 是吗  -我能跟卡尔谈吗
Five years, we 10x revenue? Yeah?   -Can I talk to Karl?
可信度的上限是多少
What is the biggest headline number that's credible?
问题是 数学不只是数学
The thing is, numbers aren't just numbers
它们是数字  -我听不懂你在说什么 彼得
They're numbers.   -That's you... you're talking gibberish, Pete.
开玩笑的 我在跟你开玩笑 彼得
I'm just kidding. I'm kidding. I'm fucking with you. Pete.
如果你觉得可怕
If it feels scary.
是因为 这其中的潜力大得吓人 彼得
it's because the potential is scary, Pete
当然 我懂
Sure. No, good
嘿 我需要你有信心
Hey, I need you to be comfortable
因为 分析师会对这一点 穷追猛打
because the analysts, they're gonna get into us on this
你有信心吗 你有信心吗 彼得
Are you confident? Are you confident, Pete?
我想这是可以的  -据理力争
I think we can make the argument.   -Dukes up?
可以说出一个道理来 是的  -是吗
We can make the argument. Yeah.   -Yeah. Yeah?
对 太好了
Great! Fuck yeah
开下门
Can you get the door?
嘿 卢卡斯 嘿 亲爱的
Hey, Lukas. Hey, Sweedey
嘿
Hey!
听着 我想应该跟你说
So... Look, I figured that I should mention
我们会极力宣传”生活+”
we are gonna be pushing Living Plus
我不喜欢房地产
I don't want... I don't like real estate
因为规模无法放大
It's not scalable,
收尾太麻烦了
and I don't want the hassle of unwinding.
你有办法阻止吗
Is... is there any way you can stop it?
不 我不行 没办法
No. No, I can't.
你要我怎么阻止
I mean, and like how?
我也不知道 你可以关灯
I don't... I don't know. You can turn off the lights
或是说 有炸弹
or, bomb threat.
听着 我跟你透露了很多事情
Look, I am being very generous telling you stuff,
因为 我觉得有鉴于目前的情况
because I feel like it's appropriate
这样做是对的
given where we're at,
但是 我不想对任何人施压
but I'm not about to start dropping stage weights on people's heads.
听着 让我想一下
Look, let me have a think about it.
好吗  -好 再见
Okay?   -Okay. Bye.
好 好 早安
Okay. Okay. Morning
很好 然后灯光照过来
Great. And then the light that comes through
情况如何  -很好 房子
How we doing?   -Good. The house
最后还是没有满足你所有的要求
In the end, the guys couldn't achieve everything
不会只有这样吧
This won't be just this, will it?
不是 外面会加一些东西
Well, no. We're... we're throwing something over it
其他的用灯光来补足
We can do it with light
云也有了吗
You did the clouds?
对  -我可以看吗
Yeah.   -Can I see'em?
可以 约翰 开灯 开云灯
Yeah. Yeah. John. Hit it. Hit on the clouds
好 工作暂停
Okay. Hold the work
各位 这不是我要的云
Guys, this... That's... That's not the clouds
这完全不是我要的云...
It's not the clouds at all.
我跟你们说过 我在柏林看过 他们...
I told you, I saw it in Berlin. It... the..
我们跟他们联络了 但是...
We... we were in touch with them, but.
就
Just...
让我想一下
et me think
你觉得呢
What do you think, man? It's
那些字 还放得下吗
It still fits? The words?
那些字 那些字 对...
The words? The words. Yes.
那些有趣的数字...
Where did those fun little numbers.
是哪里来的
Where did that come from?
从这上面 罗曼  -那上面
From up here, Rome.   -From... From up there?
嘿 预测 对吧  -当然
Hey. Projections, right?   -Sure.
开玩笑的 数字有了 数字有了 彼得 有数字了
I'm kidding. No, we have it. We have it. Pete has it.
是吗  -没问题的
Yeah?   -It's all good
是啊 大棒一挥 打到外太空
Yeah. Hockey stick, we're pushing to the moon.
对吧 罗曼
Right, Rome?
是的  -打到外太空
Yeah.   -To the moon.
嘿  -你好
Hey.   -Hello.
你对那些字有什么想法
What do you think about the words?
是的 那些字很好 都没有问题
Yeah, words are good. Words are okay
是吗  -是
Yeah?   -Yeah.
那数字呢
And what about the numbers?
是啊
Yeah.
我懂你的想法 但...
Yeah, I get the idea, but...
那些数字很大
you know, those are big numbers.
我很担心 罗曼 他的双眼有异样的光芒
I'm worried, Rome. He's... He's got that gleam in his eye.
不会有事的  -我的天啊 罗曼
It'll be okay.   -Jesus Christ, Rome.
怎么  -这很不妙
What?   -This is not good
场面 会很他妈难看
It's gonna be very fucking messy
你失控了 他也失控了  -没事的
You're out of control, he's out of control.   -It's fine
现在这里又搞不定 我想
And this is going down. I think, should we just...
今天的活动要不要取消
Should we pull the plug on today?
没问题的 没问题的 我觉得这个方法不错
It's fine, it's fine. It's a decent play, I think.
是啊 当然  -是啊
Yeah. Sure.   -Yeah.
最好是假造数字 打到外太空
Made-up numbers and... and, shooting to the moon,
和想象中的白云,  -对
and imaginary clouds.   -Yeah
老哥 拜托  -我知道 只是...
Dude, come on.   -No, I know. I just...
我觉得风险很高
I think it's... Yeah, it's high risk
但我觉得 必须硬着头皮冲
but I think, you know, we have to back it
你知道 他在台上可以为所欲为 到时候...
You know he could do anything up there. And then..
你也脱不了身
you're a part of it.
他的计划很鲁莽
Like, he has... harebrained schemes
我很爱他 但是他承受不了压力
I love him, but he cracks under pressure.
我觉得 我们应该保护他
and I think we should protect him
我们应该阻止这件事
We should stop this.
不 没事 罗曼来了
No, it's okay. Roman's here.
嘿 兄弟 快进来 嘿  -你这服务太好了
Hey, man. Come on in. Hey!   -Beautiful service
嘿 嘿  -嗨 你好吗
Hey. hey.   -Hi. How are you?
是的 很好...  -你这身打扮真帅
Yeah, good...   -Nice. Cool digs.
还为了发布会
Flight jacket.
穿飞行夹克  -对 为了发布会
For the launch.   -For the launch
要对一遍吗 我们要不要对一遍
You wanna run it, should we run it?
我不要云了
I'm not doing the clouds
我决定了 -是的 因为那不是云
I decided.   -Well, yeah. Because they weren't clouds
不需要了 不需要了
Don't need'em. Don't need'em.
用音效就好了 肯和罗曼的不插电演出
We're just gonna do an acoustic set. Ken and Rome unplugged.
先跟你说一声 我在科罗拉多更夸张
Heads up, I've gone even bigger in Colorado.
是吗   -数字漂亮到不行
Yeah?   -The numbers get crazy good
是吗 很好  -兄弟
Yeah. Okay.   -Like, dude.
漂亮到 会让你失去对资本主义的信心
It's enough to make you lose your faith in capitalism.
你想说什么都行  -我想也是
Like you could say anything.   -Right. I'll bet
我帮你做了一件
I got... I made you one.
你试穿一下  -夹克吗
But you should try it on.   -A jacket?
对 那件是你的
Yeah, yeah. Yeah. That's for you
是吗  -对
Yeah?   -Yeah
行 好  -我们要联合驾驶 所以要做飞行夹克
-Yeah, okay.  -Co-pilots. That's the idea. Flight jacket, co-pilots
我懂
I got you....
你拿到讲稿了吗  -关于这个
You got the pages?   -Well, in that case,
我得先说一下 我...
I should talk a little bit. I just...
怎么了
What?
怎么了 我想…
What?   -I think that I.
我也说不上来 也许...
I don't know. May be...
也许…
May be, like.
我们不该这么做
we shouldn't do it?
或是...也许可以延期
Or like... may be postpone?
别这样
Don't..
老哥 这真的没关系
Hey, man, it's fucking... It's okay. It's not.
该死 我们...
Shit. You know, let's...
也许 我们应该全部他妈的交给雷
Maybe we just... dump it on fucking Ray.
反正是他的部门
I mean, look, it's his division, and... you know...
但也许 不用搞得这么大
but maybe not do the whole..
这是
This... This is the...
这是 我们当初的想法
This is the... the idea, though.
我知道  -这是…
I know.   -This is the..
也许 我只是担心 我无法说服人
Maybe I'm just worried that I can sell it. I don't know.
要不要取消  -你觉得这很疯狂吗
So, do we pull it?   -You think it's nuts?
不 不是...  -不是吗
No! No. I mean...   -No?
我是说 狗日的玩具屋
You know, I mean, pitching fuckin' playhouses
和长生不死 还有 把数字加倍
and living forever, and then doubling up
都很疯狂  -时候到了 时候到了
the fuckin'numbers.   -It's time. It's time.
该豁出去了  -我明白
It’s big-swing time  -I get it
我们非这么做不可  -我知道 我知道 我知道
We have to.   -I know. I know. I know.
我只是... 也许我只是担心
I just, maybe... May be I just worry that it's..
你知道的 这些是你的话
Or that, you know, they're your words
你口才很好 你有那个技巧
You got the words. You got the fucking skills
我可能会
and I just might, you know..
这整件事 是你的愿景
It's your vision, this whole thing.
我只是… 你知道的 我可能会搞砸
and I've sort of been in... You know, I might fuck it.
天啊
Man.
我们可以改期
I mean, we could also, like, raincheck this
以后再说 看有没有别的机会
do this some other time, and see if something else comes up.
怎么  -时间差不多到了
Yeah.   -Okay. It's about time.
时间到了吗 很好,  -对
It's time? Great.   -Yep.
一定会很棒的 你绝对会博得满堂彩
It's gonna be great. It is, you're gonna kill it
我看了你的讲稿 我了解你
I read the thing, and I know you,
这一定会
and this is gonna be, you know.
祝你好运 祝你在台上一切顺利
Good luck. Break... break that leg
卡尔想要和你聊聊
Karl wants two
嘿 卡尔  -嘿 我...
Hey, Karl.   -Yeah. Hi. Just..
我是来祝你好运的  -谢了 兄弟
Just to say good luck?   -Thanks, man
而且 如果可以 我想争取一点能见度
And, just to get some visibility, if that's okay
我…听说…我的领域
I...'Cause I just heard that, more tweaks
又做了一些修正
have been made in my arena.
没问题 没问题  -好的
It's cool. It is cool.   -Okay, well,
我可以快速看一下吗
if I could just take a quick, quick peek
卡尔 现在不方便
Karl, man, it's not a good time.
不然 说给我听也行
Then if you could just talk me through it.
这样 我也能放心地支持你
Just... No, just so I'm comfortable in my own mind that I got your back
一切都没问题的 卡尔  -我们需要...
It is all good, Karl. Okay? It's all good.   -What we... we really need.
现在不方便   -等一下 稍等...
Now is not a good time.   -Just a sec. Hang on, just..
现在不方便 卡尔,  -是吗 听我说
It's not a good time, Karl.   -Really? Well, listen to me
我跟你爸是一起苦过来的
I took a lot of shit from your dad
所以 我受了他不少气
because we've been through the mill
但 我曾经在别的上市公司
But I've been the CFO of major public companies
当过二十多年的财务长
for over two decades
对生意也是很有了解的
and I know a thing or two about a thing or two
如果你毁了他的交易
And if you fuck up his deal
或是想 提出我不放心的数字
or you try to stand up numbers that I am not comfortable with
我对天发誓…  -嘿 嘿 嘿
I swear to God...   -Hey, hey, hey
嘿 别激动 别激动 我是首席执行官 你是财务长
Hey. Easy. Easy. CEO. CFO
怎么 才接手一个星期 你就想开除财务长吗
What? You gonna fire your chief financial officer a week in?
你爸才刚过世
Your dad just gone?
那你肯定完蛋
You'd be fucking toast
肯 你抓住了我的要害
You have my dick in your hand, Ken
但 反之亦然 咱们打开天窗说亮话
But I've got yours in mine. So let's get real.
如果 你在台上说了我不想听的话
If you say anything that I don't like up there
或是 让我出丑
or make me look foolish
我会大爆内幕
I'll fucking squeal
祝好运 祝你好运 小老弟
Good luck. Good luck to you, buddy
...到辩论
... To the debates
从大选之夜 到就职日
through election night to Inauguration Day
我们将全程追踪
we'll be there every step of the way
让各位 知道最新消息
Giving you all the breaking stories
独家内幕 及 全美观众所需的
all the inside scoop s, and all the expert analysis
专家分析
America has come to depend on
四年前的大选之夜
Four years ago, election night coverage
十几个电视网的播报 吸引了7140万人收看.
drew 71.4 million viewers across a dozen networks.
你是泛美网科市民 你也是泛美网科市民
" You're an ATN citizen. You're an ATN citizen."
其中 整整一半观众 看的是泛美网科
And fully half of them were tuned to ATN
今年 我们将会精益求精
And this year, we intend to do even better
带来更强大的阵容 和更清晰的视角...
with a stronger line up and a clearer vision..
他还好吗  -挺好的
How's he doing?   -Good. Good, good
这次大选 将会是美好的一年
So this election promises to be a very good year
不只是对美国民主
for America, for democracy
及泛美网科的广告收入 也是对各位股东而言
and for ATN ad revenue, and for you, our shareholders
各位女士先生
Ladies and gentlemen,
请热烈欢迎联合CEO肯德尔·罗伊
please welcome co-CEO Kendall Roy
好
Okay.
谢谢 谢谢 嘿...是的
Thank you. Thank you. Hey... yeah
责任重大
big shoes.
Big, big shoes.
责任重大 责任重大
Big, big shoes. Big, big shoes
责任重大 名声巨大 还有精神崩溃也超大
Big shoes. Big hat. Big nervous breakdown
好的
Okay.
提词机要我说“我很高兴能站在这里”
It says here on my words that, " I'm glad to be here."
我是蛮高兴的
And, you know, I... I... I kinda am
所以 谢谢提词机 谢谢
so, thanks, prompter. Thanks
不要跟提词机讲话啦 太外行了
Don't talk to the teleprompter, amateur
这样为什么不好  -不可以这样
Why is that bad?   -You don't do that.
我上次出现在这种场合
Last time I was up at something like this
是打断我们的年度大会
I was disrupting our annual meeting
现在我是首席执行官 联合CEO
And, now I'm CEO. Co-CEO
我只想谢谢各位
And, you know, I... I just want to say thank you.
我要谢谢韦斯达大家庭
I want to thank the whole Way star family
在这困难的几天 给我们
who have offered us so much love and support
这么多爱和支持
over these last few tough days
我们真的很感激 谢谢
So, yeah, we're so grateful. Thank you
这对我们意义重大 是不是 爸爸
It means a lot. It means a lot. Isn't that right, Dad?
我的天哪 这是在搞什么
My God. My fucking God
不会吧  -这些全都是新的
No way.   -I mean, this is new, this is all new.
我知道 我们有过分歧
We, we had our differences, yeah
但是 真的很高兴看到你
But it is good to see you
切入正题吧
Let's, get on with it, shall we?
好 当然...当然了
Yeah, for sure... Sure thing. Sure..
史上最怪异的双口相声
Strangest double act ever.
那可不  -他万年不变
I'll say.   -He never changes
太他妈外行了 结束之后叫醒我
Fucking amateur hour. Wake me up when it's over
我觉得 我可能看不下去
I don't know if I can... I can watch this
她说看不下去 但还是一直看
She said while watching the fuck out of it
我都能 感受到你的兴奋了 好恶心
and getting turned on. I can hear how wet you are. It's gross
天啊 肯 别这么沉重
I mean, Jesus, Ken, keep it fucking light
你根本不用担心自己的演讲
Hey, you don't even have to worry about your speech
只要 上去收拾残局 就好
You just go on and mop up all the blood
好的 听着
Okay, so listen.
今天 我要跟各位分享一项优秀产品
Today, I wanna share with you an extraordinary product
家父为此 一直努力到最后一刻
that my father was working on to the very end
这个令人兴奋的新愿景 叫做“生活+”
It's an exciting new vision we call Living Plus
对 对 "生活+”
Yeah. Yeah. Living Plus!
大环境很艰困
Look, the world's tough
很艰困 而且越来越艰困
It's tough. It's getting tougher
我们这项新产品 提供了一个避风港
What our incredible new product offers is a sanctuary
在这里 你不会觉得
It's a place where it doesn't fee
自己或父母 只是勉强活着
you or your mom or dad are surviving life
在这里 你可以享受人生
It's somewhere you're really living
生活+
Living Plus.
现在 改名为“肯德尔疯了”
Now, rebranded " Kendall Goes Woo-Woo
我已经快尴尬到 变成化石了
If I cringe any harder, I might become a fossil
我们品牌推动的生活+房地产社群
Our brand-turbo ed Living Plus real estate communities
会保证 三项不可或缺的要素
are going to guarantee three absolute essentials
第一 绝对安心
One, total peace of mind
谨慎的社区保护 和强化的居家监控
Discreet community protection and enhanced home monitoring
你虽然有钥匙 但是并不需要它们
You'll have your keys but, yeah, you won't need'em.
安全 简便 尊重
Crime-free, hassle-free, and respectful
第二 乐趣
Two, fun.
这个不错 是你写的吗
This is good. Th... Is that you?
是你写的吗 很不错
Is that yours? Very good.
韦斯达最注重的就是乐趣
Fun is what we're all about at Way star.
很多人说 这是领先全球的
You know, by a lot of-metrics, the leading entertainment brand
娱乐品牌 所以...
in the world, So...
超地方新闻 主题电影之夜
hyper local news, movie-themed events
提前试映会 泛美网科辩论 和讨论
advance screenings, ATN debate and discussions
从烹饪 到付费收视体育节目等的 多媒体活动
multimedia events from cooking to premium access sports
我们说的是 量身打造的
We're talking integrated, everyday
整合性的 生活提升
character IP life enhancement
也许 导演会带着初剪版电影上门
Maybe a director will swing by with a rough cut
明星肯定会来
Stars certainly will
电影 电视节目 娱乐设施 和体验 您可以在家
Movies, shows, rides, experiences to enjoy at home
或和家人共同享受 您的家人会不断上门拜访
or with the family, who will not want to stop visiting
如果您需要休息 我们甚至可以告诉他们 您不在家
We can even tell them you're out if you need a break
我们觉得...安全
We think... We think that security
加上娱乐 是无敌组合 对吧
plus entertainment is a pretty unbeatable offer. Right?
还有一件事
Well, one more thing
如果我说 这一切永远不会结束呢
How about I told you it was all going to last forever?
天啊 现在要上太空了
Okay. Now we're leaving planet Earth.
很庆幸没系上安全带吧
Glad you're not strapped in?
我现在还不能这么说
Well, I can't, I can't. Not quite yet.
技术还没有到位
We're not there yet
但是 我们最主要的诉求
But our central extraordinary offer
是健康和快乐
is health and happiness.
因为 以下是让这个新产品
Because here's what makes this amazing new product
几乎让人无抗拒的特点
almost irresistible
我们和科技公司 及药厂的关系
Our incredible links with tech and pharmaceutical companies
表示 可以取得 现在还是专属于
which mean privileged access to life enhancement
亿万富翁的
and extension therapies that, right now
生活强化 和延伸治疗
are the preserve of tech billionaires
但 我们可以大规模地 送到您的家中
But we're gonna deliver them at home, at scale
有目标性 也有技术支援
targeted and supported.
嗨  -我不喜欢
Hi.   -I don't like it.
是啊  -你能阻止吗
Yeah.   -Can you stop it?
怎么 你不想打造奶奶集中营吗
What? You don't wanna make prison camps for grannies?
他究竟想怎样
So, what's the game?
他现在 骑着一辆狗屁独轮车
Yeah, I mean, he's riding the bullshit unicycle.
但也许 某人能用棍子卡住车轮
but maybe someone could put a stick in the spokes?
我上台的时候
Do we have anything behind me?
背后会有东西吗  -没有
When I go on?   -I think nothing behind you.
应该就是一片黑幕
The screen wilI just be black
但 这样反而好 因为你才是主角
But that's good 'cause then it's all about you.
对
Yeah.
我们可以帮你打聚光灯
We can get a light on you
我应该... 不会是要我站在黑暗中吧
Well, I would assume... I would hope I'm being spot lit
你们知道 我爸爸是见过世面的
You know, my dad, he'd been around a little bit
没错吧
would you say?
他对这些事情的态度 很保守
He... he... he was conservative on these matters
在收入成长方面 他的说法是...
And in terms of earnings growth, he has this to say..
我相信我们的生活+房地产品牌
I'm convinced that the Living Plus real estate brand
可以让邮轮体验正式登陆
can bring the cruise ship experience to dry land
并为我们的乐园部门 带来双倍进账
and double the earnings of our parks division.
我非常兴奋
I couldn't be more excited
双倍进账
Double the earnings
好吧 这一点也不酷
Okay. That's not fucking cool.
这个…  -剪辑得很好
Well...   -That's really well edited.
我们真的办得到吗
Can we really do it?
订阅生活+服务的用户
Are people who subscribe to Living Plus support
真的能多活20到50年吗
really gonna live ten, 20, 30, 40, 50 years more?
这真的值得吗
Is it worth it?
生活+ 将会是很尊荣的产品
Living Plus is going to be a premium product.
值得吗
Is it worth it?
如果 现在问我 愿不愿意
Well, if you asked me, would I take an extra year,
多跟父亲相处一年 说那些 来不及说的话
right now, with my dad? Say the unsaid?
那将会是 无价的
That would be priceless.
对
Yeah.
我想你 爸爸 我爱你 爸爸
I miss you, Dad. I love you, Dad.
一般的反应是...  -是怎样
General buzz is...   -What? How is it?
非常好  -是吗
Really good.   -Yeah?
大家很喜欢  -行吧
People are liking it.   -Yeah.
他们居然买账了
They're likin'it.
要死 要死 要死  -怎么了
Fuck! Fuck! Fuck!   -What?
韦斯达吉祥物 带来自由
" Do derick macht frei.'
很没格调的笑话 对吧  -靠
That's a very nasty joke, right?   -Shit
对 这是...是大屠杀的玩笑
Yeah. That's, what, a... It's a Holocaust joke
看看是谁写的  -是我们的买家写的 我们可能要讨论一下策略
Look who it's from.   -From our acquirer, so we might need to strategize
取消问答时间 可以告诉他吗
Pull the Q and A. Can we let him know?
可以告诉肯德尔吗   -操
Can we let Kendall know?   -Fuck
我们应该试试  -因为他即将一头栽进火海
We should try.   -Because he's about to base jump into a buzzsaw
对 对 你在后台吗
Right, right.  Are... are you backstage?
这对你有利 因为你的报告
This is kinda good for you, 'cause your presentation,
很无趣 这下不会有人看了
not great, and so now no one will be watching.
财务细节就交给卡尔·马勒
Detailed financials I will leave to Karl Muller,
我们的传奇财务长 他来了 给他热烈的掌声
our legendary CFO, there he is. Round of applause
嗨 谢谢
Hi. Thank you.
但是...有关于整体规划的问题吗
But... but, any questions with a broader overview?
好 是拉吉
Okay, yeah, Raj
很高兴看到各位
Good to see you guys
嗨 报告很精彩 恭喜
Hi. Congratulations on a great presentation
我只想知道 你对卢卡斯·马特森的回应有什么看法
I just wanna know how you feel about Lukas Mats son's response?
他刚刚的推文吗
His tweet right now?
抱歉 我还没看
Sorry. I'm... I'm... I'm catching up.
他的推文是
Well, he's, tweet ed the words
韦斯达吉祥物带来自由
" Do derick macht frei.
那是纳粹...  -我知道出处
Which is from the Naz...   -Yeah. I know what it's from
请等我一下
Give me a sec.
好吧  -请问你如何回应
Okay.   -What's your response?
这个嘛 我不会点赞
Well, I'm not gonna fave it.
在座的各位都知道
Everybody knows here, you guys all know
我们正打算和卢卡斯交易
we're looking at a deal with Lukas.
我非常尊敬他的成就
And, you know, I have so much time and respect for what he's built
我本人 是不会说这种话
Now, personally, I wouldn't have said that
也诚挚的 对感到冒犯的人 致歉
And, apologies, sincere apologies for any offense caused
他这个人...
You know, he's...
非常欧洲...
He's very European....
如果...
And... and... and... if and
真的跟他完成交易
If and when we complete the deal
而他 取得这项产品提供的大好机会
and he gets into the incredible opportunity this product presents
我想 他的推文会大不相同
I think he'll be tweeting something different.
你可能让这件事情受到太多关注了
Maybe you're giving this too much attention than it deserves?
我知道我在做什么  -收手吧 好吗
I know what I'm doing.   -Just... back off. Yeah?
马特森他接下来会怎么做
What he's gonna do next, Mats son?
这是因此...马特森吗 不
Well, that's why... Mats son? No
上推特 发推文
Tweet. Tweeting
他是...是 不会 他处理得很好
He is... Right. No, no, he's handling himself very well.
是的
Yeah.
他很聪明 但是 我们的意思 在社交媒体上
He's smart, but we don't always come across as we intend
常常会被人误解
on social media
生活+的一个特点
And one of the things about Living Plus, actually
就是 我们认为 它将会永垂不朽
is, that we see it going beyond
它很像社交媒体
You know, it's kind of like social media
但更好一点 你知道 这是...
but it's better. You know, it's... it's..
这是在 现实世界中的 实质的 社交媒体
It's physical social media in the real world
我想 人们很渴望这样的联系
I... I think people are hungry for that connection.
我就是其中之一
I know I am.
还有问题吗 没有了?
Any... any more questions, any more? No?
他们说 我的时间到了
They're... They're telling me that's my time.
很高兴能跟各位分享
Listen, it's been so fun sharing this with you
真的很有趣
It's been so fun.
你让我怎么在他之后上台
How am I supposed to follow this?
他刚刚提出了永生的保证
He's just promised them eternal life
谢谢各位
Thank you, guys
也谢谢你 爸爸
And, thank you, Dad
我想 是时候了 时候到了吗  -现在 请欢迎
I think it's time. Is it time?   -Now, please welcome..
是的  -是的 好
Yeah.   -Yeah. Okay
泛美网科总裁 汤姆·威姆士丹
ATN Chair, Tom Wambsgans.
我在这里帮你加油 快上台
I'm here cheering you on.
谢了 兄弟  -上 上 上
Thanks, buddy.   -Go, go, go
我帮你暖好场了  -谢了 肯
Warmed'em up for you.   -Thanks, Ken.
汤姆 加油 太棒了
Go, Tom! Yes!
好极了 发表了  -发表了 你发表了那玩意 兄弟
Incredible. Launched it.   -Launched it! You launched that shit, bro
你是泛美网科市民 我也是泛美网科市民
You are an ATN Citizen. And you are an ATN Citizen
你也是泛美网科市民 我也是泛美网科市民
And you are an ATN Citizen! And I'm an ATN Citizen.
太棒了
Yeah!
肯尼
Kenny!
我就知道你没问题
Knew you could do it.
你做到了 你做到了
You crushed it! You crushed it!
干得漂亮 兄弟 你干了件大事 我以你为荣
Great work, man. You did a thing. Proud of ya.
太好了
Yes!
谢了 各位 谢谢你们来
Thanks, guys. Thanks. Thanks for being here.
我们的表现如何
How we doing?
迷因股票美得冒泡了 -别说这些 真的呢
Meme stock frothing.   -Yada-yada, on the reals, on the reals
买方和卖方 反应都很好
Good with buy side. Good vibes with sell
好的嗖嗖嗖  -彭博新闻社的报道很正面
Okay. Zoom, zoom, zoom.   -Bloomberg has positive snaps coming
开始有动静了
Seeing some movement.
老王已死
The king is dead
新王万岁
Long live the king..
两位新王 和女王
Kings, and queen.
两位新王 和女王 万岁
Long live the kings and queen
嘿 来吧 各位  -肯德尔万岁
Hey. Come on, everybody.   -Heil Kendall!
那个混账删文了
Okay, the mother fucker deleted it
他删了那则推文
He deleted the tweet
是吗 给我看 真的吗 让我看看
Yeah? Show me, show me. Really? let me see.
好 当然 给 兄弟
Yeah. Sure. Here you go, man.
在这里 看到了吗
Here. See anything?
没有 看不到了 混账
No. Nothing to see, dipshit
他删掉了 蠢货  -这样就对了 这才像话
He deleted it. Moron.   -That's fuckin' right. Now we're talking
他下来了 价格狂飙
Climbdown. Price rocket
休斯顿 我们升空了
Houston, we have fuckin' lift off
做得好 老板
Great work, boss man!
嘿  -我在这里帮你加油
Hey...   -I was here cheering you on.
太棒了 -他很特别
Yes!   -He's special
我一眼就看出来了 他很特别
I know special, and he is special
他很特别
He's special!
休斯顿 我们有个难得的人才 我们有个难得的人才
Houston, we have special. We have special
你做到了 你成功发表了
You crushed it. You crushed the launch
请你滚开点 好 你个蠢货
Fuck out of my way, please. All right, you goddamn doofus
干得漂亮
Great job.
我什么都不记得了 一切都好模糊
I don't even remember it, you know. It's kind of a blur
是这样的 因为是你的亲身经历
It's like that. 'Cause you were really in it
感觉像是…  -人形立牌
It's just like...   -Pitch bot!
在月球上漫步 你知道吗 像月球漫步
Walking on the moon, you know? Walking on the moon.
解决了 是啊 月球漫步
Worked out. Yeah, walking on the moon.
我想宣布一件
I wanna make
我觉得 很有历史意义的事
what I think is a fairly historic announcement
我相信 罗曼·罗伊 有一根小老二
I'm convinced that Roman Roy has a micro dick
而且 眼光永远是错的
and always gets it wrong
我想宣布一件 我觉得很有历史意义的事
I wanna make what I think is a fairly historic announcement.
我相信 罗曼·罗伊
I'm convinced that Roman Roy
有一根小老二 而且眼光永远是错的
has a micro dick and always gets it wrong.
我想宣布一件 我觉得很有历史意义的事
I wanna make what I think is a fairly historic announcement.
我相信 罗曼·罗伊
I'm convinced that Roman Roy
有一根小老二 而且眼光永远是错的
has a micro dick and always gets it wrong.
我想宣布一件 我觉得很有历史意义的事
I wanna make what I think is a fairly historic announcement.
我觉得 如果我们考虑要主办
I think, if we're thinking of hosting.
我不能提到 任何关于我们的事
I can't... I can't get into it. Any of our shit, yeah.?
如果你同意的话 我觉得
I think it has to be, if this is okay with you
这一定 只能是派对和策略
strictly party and strategy
一定的 绝对是
Strictly. Entirely
不过我觉得策略很性感 这也是没办法的事
I can't help it if I find strategy sexy, though.
我真的这么觉得
I do. I really do.